Sukhrob Ilyosbekov

Age: 21

Nationality: Uzbekistan Residence: Malaysia Experience: 3+ years

Email address: suxrobGM@gmail.com

Web: https://suxrobgm.net

Facebook: https://facebook.com/suxrobgm
LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/suxrobgm
GitHub: https://github.com/suxrobGM



Profile

Thinking "out of the box" to provide software-based solutions.

.NET Developer having over 3 years of extensive experience in complete software development life cycle (SDLC) involving Requirements Gathering, Analysis, Design, Development, Testing, Packaging, Deploying and Supporting of Windows Applications, Web Applications and Mobile Applications on Microsoft platform, and Game development on the Unity platform. Experience in Agile Methodology for full life-cycle of the project.

Software skills include:

- Languages: C#, Python, C/C++, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, F#, HTML, CSS, SQL
- Databases: MS SQL, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, MS Access
- Software: Visual Studio, Rider, DataGrip, Visual Studio Code, DotPeek, Unity 3D, Git
- Technology Stack: ASP.NET Core, WPF, WinForms, Xamarin.Forms, .NET Core, Blazor Web Assembly, Unity 3D, ReactJS, Django, Bootstrap, jQuery, AJAX, RESTful API, SignalR

Work experience

Pentalight Technology • Malaysia

Unity Developer

03/2020 - present

- Development multiplayer part of project.
- Integration User Interface
- Integration Photon Unity Networking
- Integration SteamVR

Freelancer.com

Freelance Software Developer

02/2019 – 02/2020

- Web Designing and Web Development.
- Worked closely with client to provide a customized website for their business.
- Design and development of various websites.
- Designing and maintaining front end for web and mobile applications.
- Writing unit tests to improve code predictability and documentation.
- Develop support tools to reduce working time from hours to minutes.
- Used coding methods in specific programming languages to initiate and improve program execution and functionality.

EC Dev Team • Uzbekistan

Game Developer

07/2016 – 02/2019

- Designing game Al logic
- Programming game mechanics
- Scripting game map
- Programming developers' tools
- Balancing game's difficulty.

Education

INTI International College Subang Subang Jaya • Malaysia

08/2019 - present

- American Degree Transfer Program
- Major: Computer Science

Tashkent University of Information Technologies Samarkand • Uzbekistan

09/2017 - 06/2019

- Bachelor of Science
- Major: Software Engineering

Awards

Top-10 team in IT Universities contest in Uzbekistan Tashkent University of Information Technologies

02/2018

• Top-10 team in contest between IT Universities in Uzbekistan

1st place in Individual ACM ICPC format contest Tashkent University of Information Technologies

12/2017

Winner in individual ACM ICPC format contest between TUIT students

Strengths

Ability to learn from mistakes • Creative thinking • Confident • Critical thinking • Working quickly • Accuracy • Solving complex problems

Skills

Programming Languages

C#

C/C++

Python

JavaScript **TITLE**

TypeScript ■■■■

Java ■■■■

PHP ■□□□□

HTML/CSS ■■■■■

SQL **BBBB**

F# ■■□□

Frameworks & Technologies

.NET

ASP.NET ■■■■■

WPF

Xamarin.Forms

ReactJS ■■■□□

Qt ■■□□

Unity 3D

ML.NET

Entity Framework

Unit Testing ■■■□

Bootstrap 4

Git **EEEE**

ADO.NET ■■■□□

jQuery ■■■■